But Dong, don't forget about
our first wedding monthsary, okay?
Fuck this goddamn life.
What time do you
think he'll arrive?
I need...
the goddamn Dollie now!
Don't you remember
anything about today?
And as far as I know,
she even prepared a surprise party
at her husband's office yesterday.
Ahh.
Zeke!
Come here! Hurry.
What the fuck?
Zeke!
Are you okay?
- Moo!
- This is yours.
For me?
- Yes.
- Yay!
Happy birthday to me!
Belated.
Wow!
I'm sorry.
Was that about...
our first wedding
monthsary, Zeke?
Then why did you forget?
I didn't forget.
Remarkably beautiful.
All I want,
is to spend a million
monthsaries with you.
Goddamn, Dollie.
Morning, Dong.
Morning.
It's time to wake up.
It's still early.
My class starts at 10.
You're just making an excuse.
You're just lazy.
No.
It's really still early.
Besides, my professor is still asleep.
I'm still sleepy.
You don't wanna wake up, huh?
Is this for me?
A Dollie doll?
Aww, so cute!
Zeke, does...
does this have a license?
The MMDA might pull it over.
So, are you awake now?
Thank you, Dong.
To help wake you up even more...
Whoa! Hey!
Hey, don't!
- Dong!
- You're going back to sleep, huh?
Still sleepy?
I'm already up, okay? See?
Hey, wait.
Dong, how did I wake up
here in the bedroom?
You sleepwalked.
Huh, sleepwalking?
By the way,
I suggest a warm-up exercise
before you walk to school.
- Bye, wife.
- Hey!
Wait!
Wait, Dong. I don't
wanna walk to school.
Dong.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
It's beautiful!
What if?
You met someone from the mafia?
What are you going to do?
Of course, I'd stay away.
I don't want to know
people like that.
I don't like people
with bad morals.
There are so many people
spending thousands at
hospitals just to stay alive.
And people like them
just kill people?
- So, you'd stay away?
- Yes.
People like that
have no heart, Zeke.
They're bad people.
And they're scary too.
What if they end up hurting me?
How cute.
He used the Dollie keychain.
Maybe I should get him
some Dollie shades too.
Oh, right.
Okay, watch this.
Roll VTR!
Happy second monthsary, hubby!
Happy second monthsary.
I have something for you.
Ta-da!
- Wow! Dollie shades!
- Yes!
Woman, I've wanted
one of these forever!
Does it look good?
It looks amazing, oh my god!
- Picture, picture.
- Game, game.
It looks so good!
Right?
Heart shape, heart shape.
Lion, lion.
Rawr!
It looks great on you!
Right, right.
Right.
What do you mean, "right, right"?
Uh...
the road we're taking.
It's the right one.
That's what I meant.
Do you want to
watch a movie later?
After your class?
Really?
We're going to the mall?
- Yeah.
- Okay. Okay, okay.
Are we window shopping?
No, why would we window shop?
When I can just buy
whatever you want?
You're such a big spender, Dong.
And besides,
there aren't any new
Dollie doll stickers.
I'm still looking for new ones.
Shit.
Huh?
You said something?
Nothing, I...
I just remembered something.
Oh, no.
Oh my god.
Could Dong have LBM again?
Because of what
he cooked last night?
I knew it.
He's so stubborn,
he never listens to me.
Hey, are you really okay?
I'm okay.
Don't worry about me.
You know?
Maybe it'd be better if you
listened to some music first.
There!
Nice!
Soundtripping!
I know you're close by.
Track me.
- Sorry--
- Fuck!
Lying next to me!
I'm yours.
Get me, get me!
Baby, I'm yours!
Shit!
Come on and get! Woooh!
There's no other fucking way.
Get me!
Come on and get me!
Aemie, stay here.
- Stay low.
- Huh?
- Why?
Music hits better when
you're ducking down.
I just need to check
something outside the car.
Okay, sure.
Get me!
Who told you to follow us?
What's taking Zeke so long?
I look like an idiot sound
tripping here by myself.
Mr. Roswell!
Oh, fuck!
Go, check on Aemie.
We'll handle things here.
That wound looks pretty bad.
Keep them alive.
Got it.
Hey! All good now?
That took forever, I was
about to skip to the next song.
Can we go now?
Let's go.
The tire just
went a little flat.
Oh, okay.
Let's go!
Zeke, are you okay?
Are you feeling sick?
I'm okay, don't worry about me.
Good luck on your exams.
Zeke.
What's going on with you?
You're so pale.
You don't look okay.
What's going on with you?
Come on, you'll be late.
Go to class.
I'm not leaving until you tell me
why you're acting like this.
Zeke, what is it?
What's happening to you?
Zeke.
Zeke, why is there
so much blood?
Why is there so much blood?
Wait.
Wait, wait.
- You don't have to do this.
- Wait.
No! No, let me!
Help! Help!
Please, help!
Help!
Help, please!
Please help us!
Help! You need
to move over here.
I'm taking you to the
hospital, come on, hurry.
Hang in there.
Move over here.
Help!
Easy.
Zeke.
Zeke, please.
Please.
Please stay with me.
Stay with me, Zeke.
Stay with me.
Wake up, please.
Zeke, please.
Please don't leave me.
Don't leave me.
Wait, wait, wait.
I won't.
Aemie.
Wife.
I love---
Please, I don't know what to do.
Don't leave me, please!
Don't leave me!
Wait, we're almost there.
Just wait.
Girls.
Oh.
You're here.
Are you going to quit now?
Or...
Can you still do it?
Where can I find
the first target?
There.
You have two weeks for each head.
Which means...
you have six weeks.
Okay.
So...
What about the third target?
You have to kill her as well, Young.
Don't tell me you're
getting cold feet.
Fuck.
Wait.
You're not going
anywhere without this.
- You know...
- Mhmm.
Since we're the next in
line to become the next boss.
Mhmm.
I think...
We should really know
the history of the Yaji Mafia.
Yes.
But how?
Even though we want
to learn everything,
only the master knows what's
really going on and the history.
Even the term Yaji itself,
I don't know where it came from.
Bullseye.
Hey, hey!
Eat something, Aemie.
Or else...
We'll both be in
trouble with Mr. Roswell,
if he finds out I'm
letting you starve.
I'll just smoke.
Oh, come in.
Thanks.
Hi Kaizer.
There he is.
Cuz, how are you?
She's my cuz, not yours.
Come on, Momo.
Cuz, are you okay?
Aemie, we got you food.
Go ahead without me,
I'll eat later.
Are you gonna eat,
or what?
Eat this, it's good.
What happened to your husband?
I can't tell Cuz what happened.
Because he'll find out
I drove by myself.
I'm dead.
Maybe we should ask her
when she's okay.
- Okay.
- She might still be stressed.
Uh, Aemie girl.
Can I talk to you in private?
This is a private room.
No. I mean, like,
just the two of us.
Oh.
This is so good.
Excuse me for a sec.
You know Kevin
and I are over, right?
It's been a week
or two, I think.
Venice.
Sorry.
I just don't know
any comforting lines.
Why did you two break up?
I found out that Kevin is
a member of the mafia.
Oh.
Well, good thing you
broke up with him.
- No.
- I know all that mafia stuff is bad.
No, no, no.
We all know Kevin
isn't a bad person.
There's only two reasons why
someone would join the mafia.
One, it's a personal choice.
Two, you don't have
any other choice.
Sometimes, there's
also the case where
they end up in it because
they're the child of a mafia boss.
Why?
Is Kevin the son
of a mafia boss?
I don't know, really.
But the truth is, he's the
one who broke up with me.
Aemie, girl. I swear, I have no
problem with him being in the mafia.
You know.
If Zeke was the same,
I wouldn't know
what to do either.
You really love
your husband, huh?
I love him so much?
How do you know that?
Am I falling in love with Zeke?
How am I supposed to know?
Oh.
Uh, miss.
I think you walked
into the wrong room.
No.
I'm in the right room.
I'm Fiona Stonehurst.
Ezekiel's girlfriend.
Wait.
Are you the hospital janitress?
Perfect timing.
Could you clean the restroom?
I'm a bit particular
about cleanliness.
So, I'd really appreciate it.
What did she say she was?
Girlfriend?
And she's even holding his hand.
I'm not losing this one.
I'm the perfect wife.
And according to
rule number seven,
don't let other girls
come near him.
How do I get rid of her?
What if...
what if I scare her off?
You shameless woman!
You've got some nerve
getting close to my husband!
Then I'll drag her.
Get over here. Get over here!
Then I'll give her a bath!
Oh my God!
Take this!
Okay! Straight ahead.
Just keep going straight!
Until you crash into something.
U-turn, U-turn, U-turn!
Left!
Oops, straight ahead!
Dead end!
Right!
Oops, oops! Straight ahead!
Maybe that'll make her leave.
Okay!
There, there, there!
Get out already!
Go, go, go!
Come on, straight ahead!
Just keep going straight!
You can do it!
Don't ever show
your face here again!
Don't come back here!
Understand?
Eyy!
Um, excuse me!
Janitress?
Aren't you gonna clean
the comfort room now?
Hmm, no.
I prefer to start cleaning this.
Ouch! Oh my effing god!
That's hot!
You bitch!
Are you aware of
the word "manners",
or do you really not have any?
I am perfectly aware of
how I conduct my actions
in accordance with
accepted norms.
What?
Unfortunately, I found that to be
the safest and most suitable way
to put a distance between
you and my husband.
So...
You're Aemie?
Obviously.
Who else would it be?
Well, Aemie,
I'm Fiona Stonehurst.
So glad to finally meet you.
Ezekiel actually mentioned
you while he was in Hawaii.
With me.
Oh!
He did?
Aw,
thanks for accompanying
my husband.
My husband.
You know what, Aemie?
I actually think that you
and I have a lot in common.
I mean, for Ezekiel
to like the both of us,
it means we have
a lot of similarities.
I don't see it.
How many years have
you known Ezekiel?
A month.
A month?
Seriously?
Okay, well, I've known
Ezekiel ever since college.
So I practically know
everything about him.
Anyway, Aemie, I think
it's time you get some rest.
You look...
you look so tired.
But don't worry about Ezekiel.
I'll take care of him.
No,
I'm completely capable of
taking care of my husband.
Oh no!
She's still here!
She won't leave!
Maybe I should
just say it directly.
So she'll get it.
I love him.
And I always will.
She said I'm a Janitress...
We can use that route.
- Yeah, definitely.
- And that car.
So this is the whole entire
map of the Grand Park Hotel.
Mm-hmm.
So we're gonna layout this map.
And assemble our targets.
Meisha!
So you're the one who ordered
those idiots to follow Roswell to Hawaii?
- Huh?
- Yeah. And?
Fuck you, Meisha!
Fiona got dragged into it too!
I didn't tell them to hurt her.
But also, I don't really care.
We may be friends, but
don't you ever cross the line.
You wouldn't wanna
see what we're capable of.
Well, fuck you too.
Then why don't you just
kill Roswell's wife instead?
Huh?
We're just following
orders from our boss.
And also, Fiona is still alive.
You're being so dramatic!
Besides, wasn't Blood supposed
to be handling Roswell's wife?
You know what happened to me
the last time I was there, right?
Oh no! Hey, Zeke!
Oh no, Zeke! Hey!
What happened?
Easy, easy.
Why did you stand up?
Are you okay?
- I'm fucking useless.
- You should've just called--
Called me.
I was going to
get you breakfast.
How many hours was I out?
Hours?
Oh my god, Dong, you've
been asleep for days.
You've probably had a
ton of dreams by now.
Meanwhile, I've been
worried sick about you.
What happened to you?
Good luck on your exams.
You're so pale.
You don't look okay.
I'm not leaving until you tell
me why you're acting like this.
Zeke!
Zeke! Why is there
so much blood?
Help!
Please, help!
Please, stay with me!
Stay with me, Zeke!
Stay with me!
Aemie.
Please, I don't know what to do!
Don't leave me, please!
Don't leave me!
Thank you, wife.
I really thought I
was going to lose you.
I'm never gonna leave you.
Unless you want me to.
Zeke! I don't!
You look like hell, wife.
Because...
I took melatonin and
coffee at the same time!
I think they're
fighting each other!
You should have woken up early.
So I could sleep properly
You should really
look at yourself.
Ah!
Hey!
You didn't even change
clothes, or take a bath?
The audacity?
Look who's talking.
You haven't showered either.
We're even.
I'm gonna go change clothes.
Wait, I'm just gonna
change clothes, okay?
Stay right there!
Don't stand up again!
Aemie.
Aemie Roswell.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Do you have an
appointment with the CEO?
Actually, no.
I'm just checking
Ezekiel's office because
I'll be managing it while
he's still in the hospital.
And you are?
Fiona.
Fiona Stonehurst.
Ezekiel's girlfriend.
Anyway, I think we need
to remove all of this trash.
It looks awful, doesn't it?
Look!
Yuck!
Don't worry about Ezekiel.
I'll just talk to him
when he comes back.
And for the meantime, I'll
take care of everything here.
I'm gonna renovate this place.
Uh, Ms. Fiona, maybe I
should call Mr. Roswell first?
Like I said,
I'll take care of
everything here.
Oh no!
Not another crazy one.
Hello?
Yes.
We need to do some
major, major renovations.
Sorry, what was your name again?
Kate.
Kate Alonzo.
Okay.
Thanks, Kate.
Hey, easy!
- Fuck!
- Easy.
You're so stubborn!
The doctor already
told you to get some rest.
Wait, wait.
You two,
who taught Aemie how to drive?
Answer me!
I don't know, boss.
Maybe it was, uh, Lamperouge.
Maybe he gave
her driving lessons.
Ah, Zeke,
a bald guy taught me
how to drive.
Bald?
Dominic.
Don't you know him?
He already has a family.
I wanna meet that asshole.
Okay.
I'm going to ask you
assholes a few questions.
How you answer them
will determine in what state
you'll be leaving this place.
It's either
you're going to be running,
or you'll be thrown
out as corpses.
The choice is yours.
Now tell me,
do you have families?
I'll assume you do.
You still wanna see them?
Yeah?
Then you better talk.
You should be thankful
that nothing
happened to my wife.
Because if she was
hurt in any other way,
I wouldn't even be giving
this chance for you guys to talk.
Now tell me,
who sent you after us?
Fuck you, Roswell.
Your father is the reason we
don't have families anymore!
Even if you kill us,
you're still going to die!
Your wife too!
The Yaji will never
stop coming after you.
Wrong choice of words.
I love him.
And I always will.
You know, guys.
She's really not
gonna let me sleep.
What exactly...
What exactly is this
thing she's calling love?
How do you know...
How do you know when
you're in love with someone?
Can I use a
call-a-friend this time?
Hmm?
Oh.
Hello, cuz. What's up?
What does being in love mean?
And...
How do you know when...
you really, truly love someone?
Oh, cuz.
You came to the right person.
I'm practically a
certified expert on that.
Okay, listen.
I'll tell you the signs
that you're in love, okay?
Okay, okay!
Oh, hubby.
Have you eaten yet?
Not yet.
Oh, wow.
You cooked.
Here is the first sign.
When you feel something different,
if he's gonna come near and touch you...
It means...
You're in love.
Zeke. Zeke, wait.
What's the matter?
You don't want to ride a car?
What if what happened
last time happens again?
Were you the one who stole
the one hundred million pesos?
I will not answer that!
This is harassment.
I agree with the CFO.
You cannot ask such questions
in front of the entire board.
That's...
that's unprofessional.
You're not needed here.
This meeting is
about the toy industry.
Which I'm helping
your wife with, Ezekiel.
Oh, so she's actually
going to help me.
Why isn't it pink anymore?
I threw out all of your trash!
I wanted it to make
it a little more...
professional?
I think you should
take a look at this
for consideration.
Good thing you stopped by again!
Good afternoon, ma'am.
We'll help you and
Dong sell these.
Really? Is that okay?
Of course!
You'll be dead soon.
Aemie Roswell.
MkvDrama.net